UNITE Legislative Department Records 6000/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Organizations: National Capital Immigrant Coalition 2003 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Retiree Health, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Health Care: Chip, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Health Care - SCHIP, 2001-2003 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- HealthCare: State Benefits Open To Unite Members, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- UNITE! Folders, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Health Care Reform Working American Families Insurance Act 2001 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Prescription Drugs, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- GASB: Gov't Acc't Standards Brd., 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Health Care Coalition 2003 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Retiree Health Care Benefit Protection Act 2001 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Re: Immigration Issues Hon. David Bonior, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- H.R. 1261, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Civil Rights, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- FLSA 108, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO WIA, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Health Care Task Force, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Health Care 108th, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Health Care Information Perscription Drugs & Medicare/Medicaid, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- California Labor Federation, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- TAA-Pennsylvania Issues 2003 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- H.R. 1261 Letters of Opposition & Concern, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- UNITE! Papers, 1998-2000 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- LM-2 2003 Field Campaign (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Tax Cuts 2003 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- WTO 2003 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Pins + Needles - from Colombia, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1)